<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Nadav Spiegelman</title>
  <id>http://nadav.is/writing</id>
  <link href="http://nadav.is/writing"/>
  <link href="http://nadav.is/writing/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2014-07-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Nadav Spiegelman</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Quick Vim Macro for Sass @import</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/quick-vim-macro-for-sass-import/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/quick-vim-macro-for-sass-import/</id>
    <published>2014-07-12T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-12T11:57:27-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since Sass @import doesn&amp;rsquo;t support globbing (without &lt;a href="https://github.com/chriseppstein/sass-globbing"&gt;this
gem&lt;/a&gt;), here&amp;rsquo;s a quick Vim macro
for importing the contents of a directory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;:r !ls modules/&lt;/code&gt; — “read” output of command into the buffer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;qq&lt;/code&gt; — record macro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insert &lt;code&gt;@import modules/&lt;/code&gt; before filename&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;ysiW&amp;quot;&lt;/code&gt; — surround WORD with &amp;ldquo; (using
&lt;a href="https://github.com/tpope/vim-surround"&gt;vim-surround&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;q&lt;/code&gt; — stop recording&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;V7j&lt;/code&gt; - enter linewise visual and select 7 lines down&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;:norm @q&lt;/code&gt; — execute macro on selected lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class="featured"&gt;
  &lt;iframe name='quickcast' src='http://quick.as/embed/dby9flaz' scrolling='no' frameborder='0' width='100%' allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;script src='http://quick.as/embed/script/0.87'&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Charlie Haden</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/charlie-haden/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/charlie-haden/</id>
    <published>2014-07-11T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-12T11:40:08-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned at a very young age that music teaches you about life. When you&amp;rsquo;re
in the midst of improvisation, there is no yesterday and no tomorrow — there
is just the moment that you are in. In that beautiful moment, you experience
your true insignificance to the rest of the universe. It is then, and only
then, that you can experience your true significance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— &lt;em&gt;Charlie Haden&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to write about Charlie Haden. I have to. I don’t want to write about his life or to try to explain how he changed Jazz music and the role of the double bass within it. Others are more qualified to do that. I want to write about the influence that Charlie Haden has had on me as a Jazz fan and as a bass player. I wanted to do it a long time ago, to celebrate his music while he was still alive. I missed that chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Haden died this morning at 10:11 Pacific Time, 76 years old. He grew up singing in the family band and switched to the bass after his vocal cords were paralyzed by polio at age fifteen. The medium changed, but Charlie never stopped singing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Haden&amp;rsquo;s playing is the perfect combination of freedom and beauty. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I first heard Charlie when I found the early Ornette Coleman records as
a teenager.
Although the aesthetic was strange, the spirit behind the music appealed to me
as an angsty metalhead.&lt;sup id="fnref1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn1" rel="footnote"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; As I got deeper into the music and the bass, I fell in love with Charlie&amp;rsquo;s sound, ears, and commitment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Suggested listening&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few albums and tracks that have been especially important to me.
It&amp;rsquo;s a very personal list, as I could never hope to represent Charlie Haden&amp;rsquo;s fifty year career as
a professional musician here. Nor would I want to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ornette Coleman&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Haden is known for the early Ornette Coleman more than anything else. I remember buying &lt;em&gt;Change of the Century&lt;/em&gt; at Borders and rushing home to
listen to it. Lots of great tracks, but two for checking out Charlie Haden are
&amp;ldquo;The Face Of The Bass&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Una Muy Bonita&amp;rdquo;. &lt;em&gt;The Shape of Jazz to Come&lt;/em&gt; is also great and known for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie&amp;rsquo;s playing on &lt;em&gt;Science Fiction&lt;/em&gt; from 1971 is ridiculously good. I especially like &amp;ldquo;Street Woman&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;School Work&amp;rdquo;, and &amp;ldquo;Law Years&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=Change_of_the_Century.jpg alt=""&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;em&gt;Change of the Century&lt;/em&gt;, recorded 1959
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Keith Jarrett American Quartet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the Keith Jarrett group with Dewey Redman, Charlie Haden, and
Paul Motian, especially the stuff on Impulse! Records. My favorite is &lt;em&gt;Bop-Be&lt;/em&gt;.
The last track, &amp;ldquo;Pocket Full Of Cherry&amp;rdquo;, is a Charlie Haden composition. The
feel is epic, as is Keith Jarrett&amp;rsquo;s soprano sax playing on it. It&amp;rsquo;s free
improvisation, and the resolution leading up to 3:30 is an example of
Charlie&amp;rsquo;s giant ears. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=bop-be.jpg alt=""&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;em&gt;Bop-Be&lt;/em&gt;, recorded 1976
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Etudes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charlie Haden, Paul Motian, and Geri Allen released a few records
together. I&amp;rsquo;ve not heard them all, but I like &lt;em&gt;Etudes&lt;/em&gt;. It has a great version of
&amp;ldquo;Lonely Woman&amp;rdquo; (originally from &lt;em&gt;The Shape of Jazz to Come&lt;/em&gt;), and a version of Charlie
Haden&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Silence&amp;rdquo;, which was also recorded on &lt;em&gt;Bop-Be&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=etudes.jpg alt=""&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;em&gt;Etudes&lt;/em&gt;, recorded 1987
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Night And The City&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love duo albums, and &lt;em&gt;Night And The City&lt;/em&gt; with Kenny Barron is one of my favorites.&lt;sup id="fnref2"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn2" rel="footnote"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Charlie&amp;rsquo;s playing is so good.
All ballads, recorded live. I play something from Charlie&amp;rsquo;s solo on &amp;ldquo;Body And Soul&amp;rdquo; every time
I play the song.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=night-and-the-city.jpg alt=""&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;
        &lt;em&gt;Night And The City&lt;/em&gt;, recorded 1996
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div class="footnotes"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;

&lt;li id="fn1"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still maintain that there&amp;rsquo;s a deep, mysterious connection between free jazz and death metal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="#fnref1" rev="footnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li id="fn2"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two other favorites are &lt;em&gt;Jim Hall &amp;amp; Red Mitchell&lt;/em&gt;, which I mentioned &lt;a href="/writing/jim-hall/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;I Concentrate On You&lt;/em&gt; by Lee Konitz &amp;amp; Red Mitchell, which I should write about some day. &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="#fnref2" rev="footnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A month with Vim</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/a-month-with-vim/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/a-month-with-vim/</id>
    <published>2014-05-26T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-07-12T11:40:08-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since starting at &lt;a href="http://somethingdigital.com"&gt;SD&lt;/a&gt; in February, I’ve been doing a lot of work on virtual machines or remote servers. I haven’t spent this much time in the command line since I was compiling my own linux kernels and fucking up grub configs as an early teen, and it’s a lot of fun. Because many of these machines don’t have an editor other than Vim and setting up SFTP for every project in Sublime Text is a pain, I decided it was time to learn Vim. Before I started, I know how to go into insert mode and how to save and quit. That’s it. As a geek, I continually hack and refine my environment and this seemed like an obvious place for improvement. So for the past month, I’ve been using Vim exclusively. And I’ve been going deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite thing about Vim (other than street cred from my fellow nerds) is that it’s a language that builds upon itself. Once I learn a word, I can string it together with the ones I already know to form sentences. For instance, hitting &lt;em&gt;j&lt;/em&gt; moves the cursor down one line. Putting a number in front of any command repeats it that many times, so &lt;em&gt;3j&lt;/em&gt; moves the cursor down three lines. Once I learn that &lt;em&gt;d&lt;/em&gt; is for delete, I can do &lt;em&gt;d3j&lt;/em&gt; to delete three lines down. As soon as I know that &lt;em&gt;f&lt;/em&gt; finds the specified character in the line, I also know how to delete everything until the next semicolon in the line by doing &lt;em&gt;df;&lt;/em&gt;, and so on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The logic of Vim as a language is very appealing and works with the way I think. As a front end dev, being able to change the contents of an HTML tag or a string in quotes in a couple of keystrokes is awesome. Being able to expand a line of HTML or CSS using two keystrokes with &lt;a href="https://github.com/AndrewRadev/splitjoin.vim"&gt;splitjoin.vim&lt;/a&gt; is borderline mindblowing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads me to another reason I’m digging Vim: its extensibility and plugin ecosystem. This is familiar from using Sublime Text, which has many awesome plugins as well. What makes it extra appealing with Vim is that by bringing &lt;a href="https://github.com/nadavspi/dotfiles/blob/master/vimrc"&gt;my vimrc&lt;/a&gt; with me, I can feel at home on any random machine I have to work on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are tons of &lt;a href="http://stevelosh.com/blog/2010/09/coming-home-to-vim/"&gt;great&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.danielmiessler.com/study/vim/"&gt;articles&lt;/a&gt; and even &lt;a href="https://leanpub.com/painless_vim"&gt;some&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://pragprog.com/book/dnvim/practical-vim"&gt;books&lt;/a&gt; about Vim that I’ve been referencing as I go, but the main thing has been to just throw myself into it. It’s been fun and rewarding so far, and has led some other geekery like &lt;a href="http://tmux.sourceforge.net/"&gt;tmux&lt;/a&gt; and learning more about &lt;a href="https://github.com/robbyrussell/oh-my-zsh"&gt;zsh&lt;/a&gt;, but I’ll save those for another day. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>All I See is Type</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/all-i-see-is-type/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/all-i-see-is-type/</id>
    <published>2014-04-04T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-15T20:39:40-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="featured"&gt;
  &lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet featured" align="center" lang="en"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This morning in the shower I thought, &amp;ldquo;pretty good soap, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know about that typeface.&amp;rdquo; I have a problem. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23typography&amp;amp;src=hash"&gt;#typography&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Nadav Spiegelman (@nadavspi) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/nadavspi/statuses/452056264835891200"&gt;April 4, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;script async src="//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My interest in typography is a product of my renewed enthusiasm for the web in the last couple of years. It goes the other way too: the improvements in typography have made me much more excited about the web. The web is providing the greatest access to information we&amp;rsquo;ve ever had, and good typography makes it palatable, if not enjoyable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That people on the web scan instead of reading is a trope in the industry. Judging by the number of people reading on their phones on the Subway, that&amp;rsquo;s already changing and it will continue to change as Internet-capable devices become more accessible and affordable. Now is the time to get ready. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The era of tiny fonts set in endless line lengths is over, I hope. It&amp;rsquo;s not just about aesthetics; a shitty presentation makes people enlist services like &lt;a href="http://www.instapaper.com/"&gt;Instapaper&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.readability.com/"&gt;Readability&lt;/a&gt; or go elsewhere, and that hurts the bottom line. Just compare &lt;a href="http://cnn.com"&gt;CNN.com&lt;/a&gt; — with obtrusive ads and headlines set in Arial&lt;sup id="fnref1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn1" rel="footnote"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; — to the new responsive redesign of &lt;a href="http://www.theguardian.com/us?view=mobile"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eBook readers are lagging typographically, and it&amp;rsquo;s starting to bother me. As my infatuation with type grows, I&amp;rsquo;m putting down the Kindle and returning to paper more often for books that I know or suspect are well designed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="footnotes"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;

&lt;li id="fn1"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s no fucking excuse.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="#fnref1" rev="footnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Reid Miles's &lt;em&gt;Blue Note&lt;/em&gt; album covers</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/reid-miles-blue-note-album-covers/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/reid-miles-blue-note-album-covers/</id>
    <published>2014-03-26T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-15T20:39:40-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Album covers are a perfect example of design within constraints: some names, a fixed canvas, a few typefaces to choose from, sometimes a photograph. &lt;a href="http://www.bluenote.com/"&gt;Blue Note Records&lt;/a&gt; has been around since 1939, and their classic covers are absolute masterpieces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reid_Miles"&gt;Reid Miles&lt;/a&gt; was the art director for Blue Note Records in the 50&amp;rsquo;s and 60&amp;rsquo;s and designed hundreds of album covers. Many featured the photography of &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Francis_Wolff"&gt;Francis Wolff&lt;/a&gt;, one of the owners of the record label. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a trip to look through the catalog and see how many of the classic albums were designed by Reid Miles. They are as cool and interesting as the music, and an inseparable part of the experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="wide" style="margin-top: 2rem; margin-bottom: 2rem;"&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="nichols.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="clarkCrib.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="hendersonInOut.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="SomethinElse.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="blakeyMoanin.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="coltraneBlueTrain.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="morganLeeWay.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="half"&gt;&lt;img src="dorhamUnaMas.jpg" style="max-height: 430px;"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more, see the &lt;a href="http://www.birkajazz.com/archive/blueNote4000.htm"&gt;Birka Jazz Archive&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.hardformat.org/designers/reid-miles2/"&gt;Hard Format&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.gokudo.co.jp/Record/BlueNote3/nnblue2.html"&gt;Vintage Vanguard&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://retinart.net/artist-profiles/jazzy-blue-notes-reid-miles/"&gt;this interesting article on Reid Miles by Alexander Ross Charchar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Branding Jazz</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://nadav.is/writing/branding-jazz/"/>
    <id>http://nadav.is/writing/branding-jazz/</id>
    <published>2014-01-03T00:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2014-05-15T20:39:40-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I was hanging out at &lt;a href="http://jalc.org"&gt;Jazz at Lincoln Center&lt;/a&gt; the other day, checking out Wynton Marsalis Septet. The music was—of course—pretty spectacular, but I was really struck by the brand identity and literature.&lt;sup id="fnref1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn1" rel="footnote"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, now I know why: the branding was done by &lt;a href="http://thegreatdiscontent.com/paula-scher"&gt;Paula Scher&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href="http://www.pentagram.com/"&gt;Pentagram&lt;/a&gt;. The brand identity was developed in 2004, and refreshed in 2010. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of photos in &lt;a href="http://new.pentagram.com/2013/10/new-work-jazz-at-lincoln-center/"&gt;this article about the refresh on the Pentagram blog&lt;/a&gt;. I like the typeface which is based on &lt;a href="http://www.houseind.com/fonts/neutraface2"&gt;Neutraface 2&lt;/a&gt;, although the filled in letters can get intense. The print pieces were done in-house at Jazz at Lincoln Center and look fantastic. Quality photography helps too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="wide"&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src="jalc.jpg" alt="Print material for JALC"&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Print pieces designed by Luis Bravo and his team at Jazz at Lincoln Center.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src="jalc-typeface.jpg" alt="JALC's Jelly Roll Roman"&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;The Jelly Roll typeface, based on Neutraface 2.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; interesting is the choice to remove “at lincoln center” from the logo. From &lt;a href="http://new.pentagram.com/2013/10/new-work-jazz-at-lincoln-center/"&gt;the Pentagram blog post&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that Jazz is recognized as a major cultural institution in its own right, the update clears away the “at Lincoln Center” and leaves the organization as exactly what it is: Jazz&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We had hoped that the organization would eventually ‘own’ Jazz and that any other explanation of the place would become unnecessary,” says Scher. “The new identity formalizes this arrangement, which was the original intent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Uh, yeah. I’ve never heard anyone at &lt;abbr&gt;JALC&lt;/abbr&gt; refer to it as just “Jazz” (like, &amp;ldquo;Welcome to Jazz. It’s gonna be a great set!&amp;rdquo;) so I’ll assume they don’t. Because to say that &lt;abbr&gt;JALC&lt;/abbr&gt; simply &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; Jazz would be fucking weird, if not sinister. &amp;ldquo;What is Jazz?&amp;rdquo; is one of my least favorite conversation topics in the world, so I&amp;rsquo;ll leave it at that. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="footnotes"&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;

&lt;li id="fn1"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="http://jalc.org"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; is nice too—much better than most Jazz sites—but a little cluttered and confusing. I like the pairing of &lt;a href="http://www.myfonts.com/fonts/hvdfonts/brandon-grotesque/"&gt;Brandon Grotesque&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.myfonts.com/fonts/garagefonts/freight-text-pro/"&gt;Freight Text Pro&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="#fnref1" rev="footnote"&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
